Goutam Behera

Frontend Developer

I'm an experienced frontend developer with a proven track record of working with technologies like HTML, CSS (Sass), JavaScript, React JS, PHP, basic Node JS, MYSQLi, Bootstrap, and GitHub. I also have a strong both frontend and backend concepts.



✓ goutam.behera466@gmail.com

9 BTM LayOut, Bangalore, Karnataka, India

in linkedin.com/in/goutam-behera-iam

. 8249914464

www.youtube.com/@GoutamCodingUniverse

github.com/AmGoutam

EDUCATION

B.Sc ITM

Bhadrak Autonomous College, Bhadrak,

2016 - 2019

12th

Netaji Subas Memorial City College

2014 - 2016 Cuttack, Odhisha

SKILLS

TML CSS

JAVASCRIPT

REACT

NEXTJS

BOOTSTRAF

SAS

MI

NODE JS BASIC

PHP

MYSQLI

GITHUB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Web Developer ExcelR Edtech Private Limited

08/2022 - Present

BTM Layout, Bangalore

Bhadrak,odhisha

Tasks

- I've been working as a Digital Marketing Web developer at ExcelR Edtech Private Limited. My main task is to make designs that are easy for users to use on all kinds of devices.
- This includes making email templates and updating Web page and add new design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and also Using Bootstrap framework.
- Helped Marking Team in building lading pages for various campaigns which in return gave best results in terms of ROI.
- I also have handsome experience with React Js and Next Js. I've created lot
 of projects using my frontend skills. I have a YouTube channel where I upload
 my projects whatever i create. I'm a coder, and my passion is my YouTube
 channel.

Frontend Developer

YRP It Solutions. 04/2022 - 08/2022

Chikkaballapur, Karnataka

Tasks

- I've been working as a frontend developer at YRP IT Solutions. My main job is to create user-friendly designs that work well on all devices.
- Connect them to the backend database. I work with clients from various industries.

Accountant Incharge

Venkateshwara Hatcheries Pvt Ltd.

09/2021 - 03/2022 Barhi, Jharkhand

Tasks

- All Type of auding activities and document verification is done by me.
- All type of customer deals along with training related work.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

My Portfolio

https://goutam-portfolio.vercel.app/

Goutam Store

https://goutam-store.vercel.app/

Goutam Textutils

https://goutam-textutils.vercel.app/

Full Stack Development ExcelR

https://excelrbygoutam.netlify.app/

PN Classes

https://pnclasses.in/index.html

My Portfolio

• https://amgoutam.github.io/Myportfolio

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

Professional Working Proficiency

HINDI

Full Professional Proficiency

ODIA

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Youtuber Coding

Travelling

Reading

Carrom

Cricket